voip.ms 2018-10-05

# Privacy policy | VoIP.ms

**DEFINITIONS**

**VoIP.ms** : 9171-5573 QUEBEC INC. located at 300-3115, Boul. de la Pinière Terrebonne, QC J6X 4P7

**Provider** : 9171-5573 QUEBEC INC.

**Website:** <https://voip.ms/>

**Third Party Website** : Any website, even though promoted on VoIP.ms’ Website, which is not owned, nor managed by VoIP.ms.

**Customer** : the account owner or any other person using the account (authorized or unauthorized).

**1.Privacy Policy**

**VoIP.ms is committed to protect the privacy and security of the information provided by its customers using its Customer Portal, visiting its website or using its services.**

VoIP.ms voluntary adheres to the Canadian association of normalization rules about protection of personal identifiable information (PII). When you subscribe to its services, you agree that VoIP.ms can, at its own discretion, modify its Privacy Policy, with or without notice. The current Privacy Policy is available on the VoIP.ms website at  **<https://voip.ms/privacy-policy.>**  VoIP.ms may, at any time, and at its sole discretion, modify or revise this Privacy Policy, and, by using its services, you agree to be bound by such modifications or revisions.

VoIP.ms shall remain the sole owner of all information it collects through its Customer Portal, Website or any other media platform. VoIP.ms shall endeavour to respect your privacy at all times, and will never knowingly publish, broadcast or distribute your personal identifiable information to any third party or entity for any reason. Furthermore, VoIP.ms will never collect any personally identifiable information unless the customer provides such information on a voluntary basis. Personally identifiable information includes the customer’s contact information such as name, address, telephone number and e-mail address. VoIP.ms will not sell, share or rent the customer’s personal information to third parties in ways other than as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. 

Please note that the present Privacy Policy applies only to our Site and Services and does not apply to any other site of other companies or organizations to which our sites may be linked.

**2\. Information Collected by VoIP.ms  **

**A:**   **Signup** : When customers sign up with VoIP.ms, certain information such as contact information (e.g.: name, email, address, etc.) is recorded via the website or by telephone.  
 **B:  ** **Payment** : VoIP.ms may keep certain payment information on record in order to keep track of customers’ transaction history. VoIP.ms will always use secure storage practices to keep this information.  
 **C:**   **Marketing research** : VoIP.ms may at times collect certain customer information for marketing research purposes. This information is used to help VoIP.ms improve its content, website and offers.  
 **D:**   **Complaints** : VoIP.ms may collect information about you if you contact VoIP.ms with a consumer complaint or request. This information may help VoIP.ms solve issues related to a complaint, which will be kept private.

**3\. Use of Personal Identifiable Information**

VoIP.ms uses the customer’s personal identifiable information for one or more of the following reasons:

(1) Personalize your experience and the content of the VoIP.ms website;  
(2) Inform you about updates on the VoIP.ms website;  
(3) Process payments and verify payment information;  
(4) Improve the content of the VoIP.ms website;  
(5) Promote VoIP.ms products and services;  
(6) Process orders;  
(7) Develop new features and services;  
(8) Fight fraud and illegal activities;  
(9) Generate invoices;  
(10) Enforce policies;  
(11) Process complaints, feedback and requests;   
(12) Improve the quality of VoIP.ms products and services;  
(13) Monitor service usage;  
(14) Communicate through emails, text messaging, phone or fax;  
(15) Advertise products and services;  
(16) Collect statistical information;  
(17) Provide technical support and updates;  
(18) Identify illegal activities or violations of the Service Level Agreement;   
(19) Provide information to third parties performing services on our behalf for our customers;  
(20) Comply with legal requirements, exercise legal rights or defend against legal claims.

**4\. Your Assent**  

Except for what is described below, VoIP.ms will not sell, transfer or reveal your personal identifiable information to third parties without your agreement, which will be given by email. VoIP.ms may have the obligation to provide your personal identifiable information to legal entities in order to take action on a warrant, court order or an investigation. Certain personal identifiable information can be communicated to third parties in order to process your order or provide what you ordered, or to process any complaint or request from you. VoIP.ms can also communicate personal identifiable information in order to help VoIP.ms to recover a debt you have with VoIP.ms.

**5\. Third-Party Sites  **

You may obtain access to VoIP.ms website from another website. In addition, VoIP.ms website may contain links to another website which may be of interest to its visitors. Websites linked to or from its website are not under the control of VoIP.ms and third-party websites may have a different privacy policy. Therefore, this Privacy Policy applies only to this website, and not to websites owned by third parties. VoIP.ms encourages its customers to read the privacy policy of each website they visit. VoIP.ms urges you to be careful when you enter any personal identifiable information online.

**6.**   **Quotes, Orders or Inquiries**

Customers may at times be required to fill out quotes, orders or inquiry forms to order or to inquire about VoIP.ms products or services. During such process, the customer may be required to provide specific information such name, address, e-mail address, phone number, payment information and other information as may be requested by VoIP.ms in the order form. This information shall be used only for billing purposes, fulfillment of orders, ongoing account maintenance and upgrades or to contact the customer regarding services offered by VoIP.ms for which they have expressed interest. 

**7.  Information Sharing**

VoIP.ms shall not use or share customers’ personal identifiable information in ways unrelated to the ones described above without providing an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. However, VoIP.ms may disclose personal identifiable information about customers, or information regarding their use of the Services or Websites to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, for any reason if, at its sole discretion, it believes that it is reasonable to do so.

VoIP.ms may also disclose personal identifiable information to bring legal action against someone who may be violating its Service Level Agreement or other user policies that may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of VoIP.ms, its customers, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities, including to comply to laws, regulations, or governmental or legal requests. In case of a security breach compromising their information, customers will be informed.

Please note that the above listed disclosures may involve the storage and/or use of personal information outside of Canada and may be subject to different privacy laws.

**8\. Sale or merger**

VoIP.ms reserves the right to transfer personal identifiable information to a third party in the event of a sale, transfer, merger, liquidation or restructuring of its assets provided that the third party agrees to adhere to the VoIP.ms’ Service Level Agreement and provided that the third party agrees and warrants that it shall use such personal identifiable information only for the purposes that it was provided for.

**9\. Security**

VoIP.ms understands the importance of protecting your information and therefore endeavours to use the most secure and recent protocols to protect your personal identifiable information collected on the website. VoIP.ms does not make any statement or guarantee on the safety of the information provided to VoIP.ms. You understand that you provide this information to VoIP.ms at your own risk.

When customers are asked to enter certain sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected through a Secure Socket Layer (SSL). When you access any secured page of VoIP.ms website such as an order form, most web browsers will show a padlock. When locked, the padlock icon on your internet browser (Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Firefox, Safari, etc.) indicates the console is running in secure mode. In this case, communications between the client platform running the console and the managed computer are encrypted using SSL.

The padlock icon is open when the page you are viewing is not secure. However, VoIP.ms does not make any statement or guarantee on the safety of the information provided to VoIP.ms. Furthermore, you understand that you provide this information to VoIP.ms at your own risk. All customer information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted to VoIP.ms agents, developers, administrators, operations personnel and other qualified employees. Finally, the servers on which VoIP.ms stores sensitive information is kept in a secure location. 

**10\. Data Integrity**

VoIP.ms’ infrastructure consists of its own servers which are located at multiple data centres throughout North America, Europe and Australia. As such, all information collected in connection with VoIP.ms’ operations are stored on this network of servers and on your chosen device. Furthermore, VoIP.ms uses a vast range of electronic, hardware, software and procedural safeguards to protect your personal identifiable information. VoIP.ms uses standard commercially accepted procedures to protect against unauthorized access to its systems. VoIP.ms restricts access to your personal identifiable information to agents, developers, administrators, operations personnel and other qualified employees who are covered by this Policy and who need to know that information to provide services to you or otherwise assist you for a legitimate business reason. We use Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”) software, which encrypts information you view, enter, or change on our website. This prevents any unwanted access or viewing of your information by third parties. However, you should be advised that VoIP.ms has no control or cannot be held responsible for data security measures provided by other sites which you have accessed using links from VoIP.ms website.

**11\. Modifying Personal  Identifiable**  **Information**

As a customer, you can change, update or delete personal identifiable information at any time in which case you can simply log in to your account, go to your profile, and use the available options for editing the information you have submitted, or you can also contact our Data Protection Officer. Please note that access to certain personal identifiable information may be restricted to comply with Canada’s Personal Information Protection Act. To modify more sensitive information such as credit card information, you can contact VoIP.ms by email, chat or phone and clearly indicate the information that you wish to change or contact our Data Protection Officer. VoIP.ms will respond to your request as soon as possible.

**12\. Consent to Receive Communications**

When you open an account with VoIP.ms, you must provide your contact information. As such, you automatically consent to receive communications from VoIP.ms such as phone calls, email or text messages, postal mail or faxes. These communications may be sent to you for informational or promotional purposes, and may include security notifications, account balance information, service changes, rates modifications, etc. However, you may opt out of receiving promotional communications at any time via your customer portal.

**13\. Information Retention**

VoIP.ms will retain your personal identifiable information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

**14\. Cookies**

VoIP.ms website uses cookies to quantify the number of visits, the average duration of each visit, viewed pages, user authentication to the customer portal and other statistics related to the use of VoIP.ms website. The cookies are simple text files stored on your computer hard disk. The cookies cannot damage nor read any information stored on your hard disk. Some parts of the website, such as the customer portal, will not work properly if your browser does not accept cookies. Consequently, your browser must accept cookies to use the VoIP.ms website. VoIP.ms uses cookies to store login information such as usernames and passwords for customers who choose the option of storing such information on their computers. VoIP.ms also uses session cookies to facilitate customers’ navigation when viewing its website during a particular online session. After closing the browser, the session cookie simply terminates; it is not stored on your computer’s hard drive thereafter. VoIP.ms also uses cookies to update and tailor its website to better meet its customers’ needs. Visitors have the option to disable cookies, which could, however, prevent them from accessing some of the information on its website. VoIP.ms does not use cookies to store credit card information.

**14.1 Why VoIP.ms uses Cookies and Web Beacons what is the purpose?**

When you visit VoIP.ms website, your IP Address is collected by Web Beacons and Cookies, such as Google Analytics cookies. This collection will help VoIP.ms produce comparable data and statistics on how the customers use our website and analyze traffic to the website in order to make improvements to them, so they can better meet your expectations. Web Beacons are also used in HTML emails to count how many emails are opened and read. VoIP.ms collects only general data that will be used only to make improvements on our website and in VoIP.ms’ communications with its customers.   
Parameter Cookies record your IP Address and browser data for efficiency reasons. Therefore, in your forthcoming visit, the said data will be automatically set.

With the Advertising Cookies and Web Beacons, VoIP.ms will be able to target your preferences and interests on an anonymous basis. These cookies record your device’s IP Address (or your device’s unique identification number) and your browsing history so that VoIP.ms can:

  * Acknowledge the features and pages you have visited and the ads you have interacted with
  * Measure the size of its audience
  * Publish adverting depending on your location and interests
  * Renew the advertising
  * Use ads that are meeting your needs and interests

The Cookies and Web Beacon will not be used to connect your identity in all cases mentioned above. 

Finally, in some cases, VoIP.ms use connection Cookies and session state Cookies in its Customer Centre and WebMail service in the purpose of storing information that you will not have to fill again, and they are in a secure zone of the website. Thus, you can proceed to your online transactions in a safe way. Session state Cookies ensure the smooth functioning of the Customer Centre, WebMail service and retaining items in a customer’s shopping cart until the transaction is complete or the customer logs out.

**14.2 How can I prevent or prohibit the creation or storage of Cookies and Web Beacons?**

By accessing and using VoIP.ms services without any express of action from the customer, you are deemed to consent to the use of Cookies and Policy Regarding the Use of Personal Information of VoIP.ms’ Website Users and Visitors. Within your browser, you may at any time totally disable Cookie storage or archiving. This will also influence Web Beacons.

  * To disable Cookies on Google Chrome, follow this link: <https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416?hl=en>

  * To disable Cookies on Internet Explorer, follow this link: <http://windows.microsoft.com/fr-CA/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-11>

  * To disable Cookies on Firefox, follow this link: <https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences>

  * To disable Cookies on Edge, follow this link: <http://windows.microsoft.com/fr-ca/windows-10/edge-privacy-faq>

  * To disable Cookies on Safari (iOS), follow this link: <https://support.apple.com/en-ca/HT201265>

  * To disable Cookies on Safari (Mac), follow this link: [https://support.apple.com/kb/PH17191?viewlocale=en_US&locale=en_US](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH17191?viewlocale=en_US&locale=en_US)

To disable cookies on your mobile phone or tablet browser, consult your phone or tablet’s user guides or the website of the Internet browser you use on your phone or tablet.

If you decide to disable all the features within your browser, VoIP.ms guarantee that you will still have access to the information available on the website, but you may be unable to use some advanced features that require Cookies or Beacons. If you encounter any difficulties of this kind, please contact VoIP.ms Technical Support.

**15\. Customer Feedback  **

VoIP.ms encourages its customers to make volunteer contributions such as suggestions, comments, or support inquiries by email, phone or chat. Customers submitting feedback agree that it shall become the exclusive property of VoIP.ms, including, but not limited to, any intellectual property or other proprietary information contained within that feedback in the form of text, pictures or any other attachment. Furthermore, customers agree to assign all rights and title in or to all feedback that you submit to VoIP.ms, in any shape or form, and execute any and all documents necessary to assign your rights to any and all feedback to VoIP.ms upon VoIP.ms’ request, including but not limited to any documents necessary to perfect its rights in and to intellectual property or proprietary rights.

**16\. Forums, blogs and wiki**

The VoIP.ms website provides its customers and visitors with a Community Wiki as well as links to Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Google+, community forums and personal blogs. It is important to note, however, that VoIP.ms cannot guarantee the protection of information you provide on these other websites or media platforms. Information posted on public forums is often hard to remove and may even remain there indefinitely. As such, VoIP.ms is not responsible for the collection, use or distribution of personal information posted on public forums. Therefore, you should always use caution before providing personal information in blogs and community forums, and we encourage you to read the Privacy Policies of such blogs and community forums.

**17\. Changes to Policy  **

VoIP.ms may revise this Policy from time to time. As such, VoIP.ms has the right to update or modify its content, or any other of its policies or practices, at any time with or without notice. Any amendment to this Policy will be posted on its website, to let its customers know how the information collected is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed. Customers are invited to review the Policy periodically to remain up to date as to its modifications. Continued access to the VoIP.ms website indicates the visitor’s assent to any changes and confirms their agreement to the terms of our Policy. Major changes to this Policy will be notified to customers by email.   
**Do not use the VoIP.ms website or any of its Services if you do not agree with these terms**. VoIP.ms may, at its discretion, change, modify, add, or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time. You should review this Privacy Policy regularly for changes by visiting its Website. If at any time in the future VoIP.ms plan to use Personal Information collected under this Privacy Policy in a way that differs materially and adversely from this Privacy Policy, VoIP.ms will post such changes here and may request your consent or approval before implementing the change with respect to Personal Information that you provided before the change in policy.

**18\. SPAM / SPIT**

VoIP.ms has a zero-tolerance policy for Spam and Spam over Internet Telephony (SPIT). Spam and SPIT complaints are dealt with quickly and firmly and may result in cancellation of your VoIP.ms account.

VoIP.ms has also a zero-tolerance policy regarding abuse and unauthorized use of other customers’ personal information, any infringement or violation of other customers’ rights, disrespect, interference or any attempt thereof with VoIP.ms’ security measures, and the use of any device or software intended to harm or access any other customers’ and VoIP.ms’ devices.

Any violation of the present Privacy Policy may result in immediate action from VoIP.ms, including but not limited to legal action and/or suspension or deletion of customer’s account and/or services.

**19\. Children’s Online Protection of Privacy Policy**

VoIP.ms Services are not intended for or directed to users under the age of eighteen (18), or below the legal age in your jurisdiction. As such, VoIP.ms does not knowingly or intentionally collect personally identifiable information from people under eighteen (18), or underage depending on the jurisdiction. VoIP.ms takes all the necessary measures to ensure that users are of legal age and to inform minors not to submit such information to the Services or in response to advertisements. Should you notice that personal information may have been inadvertently provided to or collected by VoIP.ms, please contact VoIP.ms immediately so appropriate steps may be taken to remove such information from its database.VoIP.ms does not sell products or services for purchase by children, and VoIP.ms does not under any circumstances solicit or collect PII from children or teenagers under the age of eighteen (18), or under the legal age prescribed by law by customer’s country.

**20\. Contacting VoIP.ms**

If you want to see or update your personal information, or to delete your information or for any other type of request regarding your personal information, please communicate with VoIP.ms through the "Contact us" section of its website. If you do not wish to receive emails on behalf of VoIP.ms, you can send an email with the subject "unsubscribe" at [support@voip.ms](mailto:support@voip.ms).

For any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may, at any time, reach out to VoIP.ms at the following e-mail address: [legal@voip.ms](mailto:legal@voip.ms).
